smartnetworld.com 2011-12-19

# Privacy Policy | Smart business solutions, internet marketing information, web tools, software, products and more for a successful and profitable online home based business

**Preamble**

SmartNetWorld Enterprises, the owner of the domain smartnetworld.com and herewith referred as Our Company understands that you may have concerns about safeguarding your privacy on-line. The Privacy Statement that follows explains our views and practices concerning privacy, and how they may pertain to you as you make full use of our many offerings. This statement discloses the privacy practices for all of our websites including the website you are currently visiting where you are reading this Privacy Policy.

**Article 1. Collection of Personal Information from Site Visitors**

Our Company automatically collects and/or tracks (1) the home server domain names, IP address, e-mail addresses, type of client computer, and type of Web browser of visitors to Our Company’s Web site, (2) the e-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with Our Company via e-mail, (3) information such as personal, financial or demographic information, knowingly provided by the visitor in on-line forms, registration forms, surveys, and sweepstakes entries, and (4) information, either in the aggregate or user specific, on what pages visitors access.

Our Company places Internet cookies on visitors’ hard drives. We use cookies to deliver information and content specific to your interests, and to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. Internet cookies save the visitor’s name, password, user-name, screen preferences, the pages of our Web site viewed by the visitor, and the advertisements viewed or clicked by the visitor. When the visitor revisits our Web site, Our Company will recognize the visitor by the Internet cookie and customize the visitor’s experience accordingly. Internet cookies are stored on the visitor’s hard drive and are not stored, in any form, by Our Company. Visitors may decline the Internet cookie by using the appropriate feature of their Web browser software, if available.

**Article 2. Use of Personal Data Collected**

Personal data collected by Our Company will be used by Our Company for editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of users’ behavior, for future product development, for content improvement, to inform advertisers as to how many visitors have seen or clicked their advertisements, and to customize content and layout of Our Company’s site. Names, postal and e-mail addresses, and phone numbers collected may be added to Our Company’s databases and used for future e-mails, calls and mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and status of orders placed online. Financial information collected may be used to check the user’s qualifications for registration, to bill the user for products and services, to notify the user in the event of sweepstakes winnings, and to notify the relevant taxing and regulatory authorities regarding payments or prizes.

Demographic and profile data collected is used to tailor the visitor’s experience at our site, enabling us to present content we think they might be interested in. We use customer contact information to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer’s contact information is also used to contact him or her in the event of a sweepstakes winning, and to notify the relevant taxing and regulatory authorities regarding payments or prizes.

**Article 3. Disclosure of Personal Data to Third Parties**

Our Company reserves the right to share, rent, sell, or otherwise disclose data it collects on Our Company’s Web site to third parties. Any third party to which Our Company shares, rents, sells, or otherwise discloses personal data will be carefully pre-screened by Our Company, determined by Our Company to be reputable, and will use the personal data for marketing products and services which Our Company determines, in its sole judgment, that visitors might find of interest. Our Company will disclose to third parties information knowingly and voluntarily disclosed by visitors, or information in aggregate form.

Through the use of third party cookies, an advertiser will be electronically notified when visitors view or click on its advertisements. This site contains links to other sites and Our Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.

**Article 4. The Use of Cookies on This Site**

Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. Our Company uses Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Authorized Customers. For example, if an Authorized Customer is logged on and the site is unused for more than 10 minutes, we will automatically log the Authorized Customer off.

Third Party Cookies

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may place or recognize a unique cookie, or other technology, on your browser. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Third Party Advertising

Our Company uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. Some ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by [DoubleClick advertising](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx). Information about your visit to their site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used, please click here: <http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy> In addition, you may choose to opt out of the DoubleClick cookie at any time by using [DoubleClick’s opt-out cookie](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Our Company does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

**Article 5. Opt-Out Right**

We allow users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we voluntary request information about the visitor. This site also allows users to remove their information from our database. If a user removes his or her information from the Our Company database it will no longer be used by Our Company for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by Our Company or third parties to send promotional correspondences to the visitor. Users can remove their information by writing to us via postal mail at the address below, or by sending an email requesting removal to admin at smartnetworld.com (replace at with @)

Visitors may opt out of having their personal information collected by Our Company, by contacting Our Company via postal mail to the address below, or via e-mail to admin at smartnetworld.com (replace at with @)

**Article 6. Access to and Ability to Correct Personal Data**

Upon request via postal mail or e-mail, Our Company will provide to visitors a summary of any personal information retained by Our Company regarding the visitor. Our Company will only send personal records to the e-mail address on file for the visitor name associated with it. Visitors may modify, correct, change, or update their personal record or cause their personal record to be removed from Our Company’s database. Visitors may change or modify information previously provided by contacting Our Company via postal mail to the address below, or via e-mail to admin at smartnetworld.com (replace at with @).

**Article 7. Collection of Personal Data from Children**

The information and services provided at Our Company’s web site by Our Company, its affiliates, sponsors, and advertisers are not intended to be viewed by children under 13 years of age. All sweepstakes offered at Our Company are open to United States residents 18 years or older only. Our Company will not knowingly permit a child to participate in a game, offering of a prize, or another activity. If a child wins a sweepstakes, that child’s entry will be voided, and another winner will be drawn.

Concerning visitors to its site that it knows are children under 13 years of age, Our Company maintains the following policies:

***** Our Company will not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age without prior parental consent, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, on-line information will only be used to respond directly to the child’s request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent.

***** In the event a child submits information to the Our Company Web site, the child must provide an e-mail address for the child’s parent or guardian. Thereafter, Our Company will send an e-mail to the parent or guardian alerting them to the child’s registration and providing instructions on how the parent can provide consent for the child to view the contents of Our Company, or how the parent could view or delete the child’s registration, if so desired.

***** Our Company will not knowingly distribute to third parties any personally identifiable offline contact information concerning children under 13 years of age without prior parental consent.

***** No information collected from children is knowingly used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside Our Company.

**Article 8. Our Company’s Right to Contact User**

Our Company reserves the right to contact site visitors regarding account status and changes to subscriber agreements, privacy policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to site visitors.

**Article 9. Our Company’s Right to Change Privacy Policy**

Our Company reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying visitors of the existence and location of the new or revised privacy policy.

**Contacting Our Company**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact:  
SmartNetWorld Enterprises  
326 One Tree Point Road  
Whangarei, 0118  
New Zealand

**Article 10. Links**

This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.

**Article 11. Disputes**

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by New Zealand law. If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: Whangarei, New Zealand. Any costs and fees other than attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared equally by each of us.

If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the following location: Whangarei, New Zealand under the rules of the New Zealand Arbitration Association. Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any court with jurisdiction to do so.

This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

© 2004 – 2011 SmartNetWorld Enterprises , All rights reserved.  
Unauthorized duplication or publication of any materials from this Site is expressly prohibited.
